Guide to the H. Elliott McClure Papers, 1947-1989.
McClure, H. Elliott papers
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
H. Elliott McClure papers, 1947-1989.
6757
Elliott. McClure
28 cubic ft.
Correspondence, Photographs, Printed Materials, Research Materials
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Files relating to Asian birds include species files and lists from Japan and India; files relating to bird banding, especially in Thailand.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Ornithologist.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Files relating to Asian birds include species files and lists from Japan and India; files relating to bird banding, especially in Thailand; letters from people throughout Asia describing banded birds they recovered; files relating to the Migratory Animal Pathological Survey (MAPS); files on ectoparasites of birds and rodents in Asia; correspondence; photographs; diary; trip/conference reports; publications, particularly annual reports of the U.S. Army Medical Research Lab, the Armed Forces Institute of Pathology, and MAPS.
Spiral notebook, with a hand-written summary table of every species McClure himself banded over 50 years (74,092 individuals of 525 species).
SUBJECTS
Names:
McClure, Elliott.; Armed Forces Institute of Pathology (U.S.); Migratory Animal Pathological Survey.; Migratory Animal Pathological Survey.; United States.Army Medical Research Laboratory, Fort Knox Ky.
Subjects:
Birds--Japan.; Bird banding.; Birds--Asia.; Birds--India.; Birds--Migration.; Birds--Parasites.; Birds as carriers of disease.; Ornithologists--United States.; Entomologists--United States.
Form and Genre Terms:
Photographs.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
SERIES LIST
Series I: Species Files and Banding Lists
Series II: Banding Lists, Counts and Observation Files
Series III: Bird Banding - Khao Yai Bird Studies (Thailand)
Series IV: Avian Disease: Parasites and Ectoparasites
Series V: Recovery Files
Series VI: Arthropods
Series VII: Diaries and Correspondence
Series VIII: Trip/Conference Reports
Series IX: Organizations - Defenders of Wildlife
Series X: Migratory Animals Pathological Survey
Series XI: Manuscripts and Drafts
Series XII: Papers and Reprints
Series XIII: Publications and reports: US Army
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I: Species Files and Banding Lists
  - Birds from Japan, Bharatpur (India) and Malaysia
    - Pintail (Anas acuta) (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Shoveller (Anas clypeata) (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Teal (Anas crecca) (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Falcated Teal (Anas falcata) (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Spectacled Teal (Anas formosa) (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Wigeon (Hidori gamo) (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Spot-billed Duck (Anas poecilorhyncha) (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Garganey (Anas querqudula) (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Gadwall (Anas strepera) (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - White-fronted Goose (Anser erythropus) (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Pochard (Arthya ferina) (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Tufted Duck (Aythya fuligula) (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Bean Goose (Anser fabalis) (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Swans (Anser cygnoides) (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Cotton Teal (Nettapus coromandelianus) (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Mandarin Duck (Aix galericulate) (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Black Scoter (Melanitta nigra) (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Niltava (Muscicava grandis) (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - White-tailed Blue Flycatcher (Muscicapa concreta) (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - Japanese Blue Flycatcher (Muscicapa cyanomelana) (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - Grey-spotted Flycatcher (Muscicapa griseisticta) (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - Mugimaki Flycatcher (Muscicapa mugimaki) (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - Rufous-breasted Flycatcher (Muscicapa hyperythra) (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - Narcissus Flycatcher (Muscicapa narcissina) (Box 1, Folder 57)
    - Ferruginous Flycatcher (Muscicapa rufilata) (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - Blue and Orange Flycatcher (Muscicapa sundara) (Box 1, Folder 59)
    - White-bellied Blue Flycatcher (Muscicapa tickelliae) (Box 1, Folder 60)
    - White Throated Jungle Flycatcher (Rhinomyias umbriatilis) (Box 1, Folder 61)
    - Japanese Paradise Flycatcher (Terpsiphone atrocaudata) (Box 1, Folder 62)
    - Mangrove Blue Flycatcher (Muscicapa rufigastra) (Box 1, Folder 63)
    - Mountain Fantail Flycatcher (Phipidura albicollis) (Box 1, Folder 64)
    - Marron Breasted Flycatcher (Philentoma velata) (Box 1, Folder 65)
    - Jungle Flycatcher (Box 1, Folder 66)
    - Chestnut-winged Flycatcher (Philentoma pyrhoptera) (Box 1, Folder 67)
    - Pale Blue Flycatcher (Muscicapa unicolor) (Box 1, Folder 68)
    - Migratory Jungle Flycatcher (Rhinomyias brunneata) (Box 1, Folder 69)
    - Mangrove Flycatcher Shrike (Pachycephala cinera) (Box 1, Folder 70)
    - Japanese Wagtail (Motacilla grandis) (Box 1, Folder 71)
    - Grey Wagtail (Motacilla cinerea) (Box 1, Folder 72)
    - Forest Wagtail (Dendronanthus indica) (Box 1, Folder 73)
    - Pied Wagtail (Motacilla alba) (Box 1, Folder 74)
    - Blue-headed Wagtail (Motacilla flava) (Box 1, Folder 75)
    - Malay Pipit (Anthus noraezeclandiae) (Box 1, Folder 76)
    - Water Pipit (Anthus spinoletta) (Box 1, Folder 77)
    - Tree Pipit (Anthus hodgsoni) (Box 1, Folder 78)
    - Tree Pipit (Anthus hodgsoni) (Box 1, Folder 79)
    - Red-headed Tailor Bird (Orthotomus sericeus) (Box 1, Folder 80)
    - Ashy Tailor Bird (Orthotomus ruficeps) (Box 1, Folder 81)
    - Orange-bellied Flowerpecker (Dicaeum Trigonostigma) (Box 1, Folder 82)
    - Fire-breasted Flowerpecker (Dicaeum sanguinolentum) (Box 1, Folder 83)
    - Scarlet-backed Flowerpecker (Dicaeum cruentatum) (Box 1, Folder 84)
    - Yellow -throated Flowerpecker (Dicaeum concolor) (Box 1, Folder 85)
    - Crimson-breasted Flowerpecker (Pronochilus percussus) (Box 1, Folder 86)
    - Scarlet-breasted Flowerpecker (Pronochilus thoracicus) (Box 1, Folder 87)
    - White Eye (Zosterops palpebrosa) (Box 1, Folder 88)
    - Hedge Sparrow (Prunella rubida); Rock Accentor (Prunella collaris) (Box 1, Folder 89)
    - Orange-breasted Flycatcher (Muscicapa hodgsoni) (Box 1, Folder 90)
    - Glossy Starling (Aplonis panayensis) (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Glossy Tree Starling (Alponis panayensis) (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Gold-breasted Mynah (Ampeliceps coronatus) (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Chinese Starling (Sturnia sinensis) (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Red-cheeked Starling (Sturnus philippensis) (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Common Mynah (Sturnus tristis) (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Pied Starling (Sturnus contra) (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Black-collared Mynah (Sturnus nigricollis) (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Tiong (Gracula religiosa) (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Daurian Starling (Sternus sterninus) (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Chinese-cresetd Mynah (Acridotheres cristatellus) (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Buffalo Mynah (Acridotheres fuscus) (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Grey Starling (Sturnus cineraceus) (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Little Spider-hunter (Arachnothera longirostris) (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Long-billed Spider-hunter (Arachnothera longirostris) (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Lesser Yellow-eared Spider-hunter (Arachnothera chrysogenys) (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Grey-breasted Spider-hunter (Arachnothera affinis) (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Greater Yellow-eared Spider-hunter (Arachnothera crassirostris) (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Streaked Spider-hunter (Arachnothera magna) (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Thick-billed Spider-hunter (Arachnothera robusta) (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Crimson Sunbird (Aethopyga siparaja); Scarlet Sunbird (Aethopyga mystacallis) (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Yellow-breasted Sunbird (Nectarina jugularis) (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Purple-throated Sunbird (Leptocoma brasiliiane) (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Purpple-naped Sunbird (Hyppograma hyppogramica) (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Ruby-cheeked Sunbird (Anthreptes singalensis) (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Plain-colored Sunbird (Anthreptes simplex) (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Black-breasted Sunbird (Aethopyga saturata) (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Brown-throated Sunbird (Anthreptes malacensis) (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Copper-throated Sunbird (Nectarinia chalcostetha) (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Chinese Goose (Cygnopsis cygnoid) (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Mallard (Anas platyrhynchos) (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Scaup Duck (Aythya marila) (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Golden-eye (Bucephala clangula) (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Harlequin Duck (Histrionicus histrionicus) (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Old Squaw Duck (Clangula hyemalis) (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Red-breasted Merganser (Mergus serrator) (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Velvet Scoter (Melanitta fusca) (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Grey-backed Shrike (Lanius nascatus) (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Brown Shrike (Lanius cristatus) (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Bull-headed Shrike (Lanius bucephalus) (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Thick-billed Shrike (Lanius excubitor) (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Waxwings (Bombycillidae) (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Red Fantail Flycatcher (Rhipidura javanica) (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Cedar Waxwing (Bombycilla cedrorum) (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Loggerhead Shrike (Lanius ludovicianus) (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Phainopepla(Phainopepla nitens) (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Columbidae
    - Spotted Dove(Streptopelia chinensis); Columbidae list (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Mountain Imperial Pigeon (Ducula badia) (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Pink-headed Fruit Dove (Ptilinopus jambu) (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Wedge-tailed Green Pigeon (Treron sphenura) (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Little Green Pigeon (Treron olax) (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Pink-necked Green Pigeon (Treron vernans) (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Domestic Pigeon (Columba livia) (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Doves (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Turtle Dove (Streptophelia chinensis) (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Ring-necked Dove (Streptophelia decaoto) (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Siebolds Green Pigeon (Sphenurus sieboldii) (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Nicobar Pigeon (Caloenas nicobarica) (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Pied Imperial Pigeon (Ducula bicolor) (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Burmese Red Turtle Dove (Streptophelia tranouebarica) (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Cinnamon-headed Green Pigeon (Treron fulvicollis) (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Grey Wood Pigeon (Columba janthina) (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Spotted Dove (Streptophelia chinensis) (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Barred Ground Dove (Geopelia striata) (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Little Cuckoo Dove (Macropygia ruficeps); Large Cuckoo Dove (Macropygia unchall) (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Lesser thick-billed Green Pigeon (Treron curvirostra) (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Ring-necked Dove (Streptophelia decaocto) (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Emerald Dove (Chalcophaps indica) (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Cuculidae
    - Chestnut-breated Malkoha (Phoenicophaeus curvirostris) (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Drongo Cuckoo (Surniculus lugubris) (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Large Green-billed Malhoka (Rhopodytes tristis) (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Roadrunner (Geococcyx californianus) (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Yellow-billed Cuckoo (Coccyzus americanus) (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Indian Cuckoo(Cuculus micropterus) (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Large Hawk-cuckoo (Cuculus fugax) (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Violet Cuckoo (Chalcites xanthorynchus) (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Red-winged Crested Cuckoo (Clamator coromandus) (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - Fantail cuckoo (Cacomantis variolosis) (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - Lesser Cuckoo (Cuckulus poliocephalus) (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - Himalayan Cuckoo (Cuculus saturatus) (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - Koel (Eudynamys scolopacaea) (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - Malay Cuckoo (Chrysococcyx malayanus) (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - Common Cuckoo (Cuculus canorus) (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - Brain-fever Bird (Cocomantis merulinus) (Box 3, Folder 57)
    - Banded Bay Cuckoo (Panthoceryx sonneratii) (Box 3, Folder 58)
    - Emerald Cuckoo (Chalcites maculatus) (Box 3, Folder 59)
    - Lesser Green-billed Malhoka (Phaenicophaeus diardi) (Box 3, Folder 60)
    - Red-billed Malkoha (Phaenicopheus javanicus) (Box 3, Folder 61)
    - Raffles Malkoha (Phaenicophaeus chloropheus) (Box 3, Folder 62)
    - Rufous-bellied Malkoha (Phaenicophaeus sumatranus) (Box 3, Folder 63)
    - Large Crow Pheasant (Centropus sinensis) (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Lesser Crow Pheasant (Centropus toulu) (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Picidae
    - Red-shafted Flicker (Colaptes cafer) (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Corn Woodpecker (Melanerpes formicivorus) (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Lewis Woodpecker (Melanerpes lewis) (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Red-breasted Sapsucker (Sphyrapicus ruber) (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Downy Woodpecker (Dryobates pubescens) (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Nuttall's Woodpecker (Dryobates nutatallia) (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Hondo Pygmy Woodpecker (Dendrocopos kizuki) (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - White-backed Woodpecker (Dendrocopos leucotos) (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Spotted Woodpecker (Dendrocopos major) (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Black-naped Green Woodpecker (Picus canas) (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Green Woodpecker (Picus avokera) (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Wryneck (Jynx torquilla) (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Alaudidae
    - Horned lark (Otocaris alpestris) (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Skylark (Alauda arvensis) (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Eurylaimidae
    - Banded Broadbill (Eurylaimus javanicus) (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Black and Red Broadbill (Cymbirhynchus macrorhynchus) (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Black and Yellow Broadbill (Eurylaimus ochromalus) (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Green Broadbill (Calyptomena viridis) (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Green Broadbill (Calyptomena viridis) (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Long-tailed Broadbill (Psarisomus dalhousiae) (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Dusky Broadbill (Corydon sumatranus) (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Pittidae
    - Green-breasted Pitta (Pitta reichenowi); Hooded Pitta(Pitta sordida) (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Giant Pitta (Pitta caerulea) (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Banded Pitta (Pitta guajana) (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Greater Blue-winged Pitta (Pitta moluccensis) (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Lesser Blue Pitta (Pitta cyanea) (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Tyrannidae
    - Western Wood Pewee (Myiochanes richardsoni) (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Western Flycatcher(Empidonax difficilis) (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Ash-throated flycatcher (Myiochanes cinerascens) (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Eastern Kingbird (Tyrannus tyrannus) (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Say's Phoebe (Sayornis saya) (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Black Phoebe (Sayornis nigricans) (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Western Kingbird (Tyrannus verticalis) (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Sylviidae
    - Grey-breasted Flycatcher Warbler (Seicercus castaniceps) (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Timminck's Crowned Willow Warbler (Phylloscopus occipitalis) (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Davison's Flycatcher Warbler (Seicercus montis) (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Black-browed Reed Warbler (Acrocephalus bistrigiceps) (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Great Reed Warbler (Acrocephalus arundinaceus) (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Streaked Fantail Warbler (Cisticola juncidis) (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Bush Warbler (Cettia diphone) (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Crowned Willow Warbler (Phylloscopus ilimae) (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Fly-eater (Gerygone fusca) (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Arctic Willow Warbler (Phylloscopus borealis) (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Pale-legged Willow Warbler (Phylloscopus tenellipes) (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Pallas Grasshopper Warbler (Locustella certhiola) (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Ashy-naped Warbler (Phyllergates cucullatus) (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Streaked Grasshopper Warbler (Locustella ochotensis) (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Swamp Warbler (Locustella pryeri) (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Yellow-bellied Wren Warbler (Prinia flaviventris) (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Green Flycatcher Warbler (Phylloscopus trivirgatus) (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Ruby-crowned Kinglet (Regulus calendula) (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Gold-crowned Kinglet (Regulus satrapa) (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Goldcrest (Regulus regulus) (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Blue-grey Gnatcatcher (Polioptila caerulea) (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Chloropseidae
    - Orange-bellied Leafbird (Chloropsis hardwickii) (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Yellow headed Green Leafbird (Chloropsis cochinchinensis) (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Greater Green Leafbird (Chloropsis sonnerati) (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Lesser Green Leafbird (Chloropsis cyanopogon) (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Aegithinidae
    - Great Iora (Aegithina lafresnayei) (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Gren Iora (Aegithina viridissima) (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Common Iora (Aegithina tiphia) (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Apodidae
    - Robinson's Swiftlet (Collacalia maxima) (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Giant Swiftlet (hydrochous gigas) (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - White-bellied Swiftlet (Collocalia esculenta) (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Southern Grey-rumped Swiftlet (Collocalia francica) (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Migrant Swiftlet (Apus pacificus) (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Palm Swift (Cypsiurus parvus) (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Humes Swiftlet (Collocalia fuciphaga) (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Brown-rumped Swiftlet (Collocalia vestita) (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Large White-rumped Swift (Micropus pacificus) (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - House Swift (Apus affinis) (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Spinetail Swift (Chaetura giguntea) (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Grey-rumped Spine Tail Swiftlet (Chaetura leucopygialis) (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - White-throated Swift (Aeronautes saxatalis) (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Vaux Swift (Chaetura vauxi) (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Emberizidae
    - Brown Bullfinch (Pyrrhula nipalensis) (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Reed Bunting (Emberiza yessoensis) (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Grey Bunting (Emberiza variabilis) (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Rustic Bunting (Emberiza rustica) (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Grey-headed Bunting (Emberiza fucata) (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Meadow Bunting (Emberiza cioides) (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Yellow Bunting (Emberiza sulphurata) (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Yellow-throated Bunting (Emberiza leucocephala) (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Japanese Bunting (Emberiza spodocephala) (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Brambling (Fringilla montifringilla) (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Crossbill (Loxia curvirostra) (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Bullfinch (Pyrrhula pyrrhula) (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Long-tailed Rose Finch (Uragus sibiricus) (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Siskin (Carduelis spinus) (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Greenfinch (Chloris sinica) (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Grosbeak (Eophona personata) (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Hawfinch (Coccothraustes coccothraustes) (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Swinhoe's Reed Bunting (Emberiza schoeniclus) (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Redpoll (Acanthis Flammaea); Pallas' Rosy Finch (Carpodacus roseus) (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Scolopacidae
    - Greater Yellowlegs (Tringa melanoleuca) (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Mountain Plover (Charadrius montanus) (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Wilson Snipe (Capella delicata) (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Long-billed Curlew (Numenius americanus) (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Spotted Sandpiper (Actitis macularia) (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Solitary Sandpiper (Tringa solitaria) (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Western Sandpiper (Ereunetes mauri) (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Least Sandpiper (Pisobia minutilla) (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - Bar-tailed Godwit (Limosa lapponica) (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - Black-tailed Godwits (Limosa limosa) (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - Common Sandpiper (Actitus hypoleucos) (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - Red-necked Stint (Calidris ruficollis) (Box 14, Folder 37)
    - Pintail Snipe (Capella stenura) (Box 14, Folder 38)
    - Green Shank (Tringa nebularia) (Box 14, Folder 39)
    - Green Sandpiper (Tringa ochropus) (Box 14, Folder 40)
    - Wood Sandpiper (Tringa glareolia) (Box 14, Folder 41)
    - Wandering Tatter (Tringa incan) (Box 14, Folder 42)
    - Red Shank (Tringa erythropus) (Box 14, Folder 43)
    - Avocet Sandpiper (Xenus cinereus) (Box 14, Folder 44)
    - Eastern Curlew (Numenius arquata) (Box 14, Folder 45)
    - Australian Curlew (Numenius madagascariensis) (Box 14, Folder 46)
    - Eastern Whimbrel (Numenius phaeopus) (Box 14, Folder 47)
    - Eastern Dunlin (Calidris alpina) (Box 14, Folder 48)
    - Pectoral Sandpiper (Calidris acuminata) (Box 14, Folder 49)
    - Broad-billed Sandpiper (Eurynorhynchus pygmeus) (Box 14, Folder 50)
    - Woodcock (Scolopax rusticola) (Box 14, Folder 51)
    - Common Snipe (Gallingo gallingo) (Box 14, Folder 52)
    - Red-breasted Snipe (Limnodromus grisens) (Box 14, Folder 53)
    - Sanderling (Calidris alba) (Box 14, Folder 54)
    - Grey-rumped Sandpiper (Heteroscelus brevipus) (Box 14, Folder 55)
  - Phalaropodidae
    - Grey Phalarope (Phalaropus fulicarius); Red-necked Phalarope (Phalaropus lobatus) (Box 14, Folder 59)
  - Recurvirostridae
    - Avocet (Recurvirostra americana) (Box 14, Folder 60)
    - Black-necked Stilt (Himantopus mexicanus) (Box 14, Folder 61)
    - Black-winged Stilt (Himantopus himantopus) (Box 14, Folder 62)
  - Glareolidae
    - Eastern Pratinicole (Glareola pratinicola) (Box 14, Folder 63)
  - Stercoraridae
    - Stercorarius (Skuas and Jaegers) (Box 14, Folder 64)
  - Rallidae
    - Coot (Fulica atra) (Box 14, Folder 65)
    - Moorhen (Gallinula chloropus) (Box 14, Folder 66)
    - Grey-bellied Crake (Porzana cinerea) (Box 14, Folder 67)
    - Ruddy Crake (Porzana fusca) (Box 14, Folder 68)
    - Banded Crake (Rallina fosciata) (Box 14, Folder 69)
    - Water Rail (Rallus aquaticus) (Box 14, Folder 70)
    - Purple Coot (Porphyrio alba) (Box 14, Folder 71)
    - Dwarf Crake (Porzana pusilla) (Box 14, Folder 72)
    - Purple Gallinule (Poryphrio martinica) (Box 14, Folder 73)
    - Water Cock (Gallicrex cineria) (Box 14, Folder 74)
    - Slaty-breasted Rail (Rallus striatus) (Box 14, Folder 75)
    - White-breasted Water Hen (Amaurornis phoeniearus) (Box 14, Folder 76)
  - Heliornithidae
    - Masked Finfoot (Heliopais personata) (Box 14, Folder 79)
  - Jacanidae
    - Bronze-winged Jacana (Metopidius indicus) (Box 14, Folder 80)
    - Pheasant-tailed Jacana (Hydrophasianus chirugus) (Box 14, Folder 81)
  - Charadriidae
    - Killdeer (Oxyechus vociferus) (Box 14, Folder 82)
    - Turnstone (Arenaria interpres) (Box 14, Folder 83)
    - Little Ring Plover (Charadrius dubius) (Box 14, Folder 84)
    - Black-bellied Plover (Charadrius squatarola) (Box 14, Folder 85)
    - Kentish Plover (Charadrius alexandrinus) (Box 14, Folder 86)
    - Mongolian Plover (Charadrius mongolus) (Box 14, Folder 87)
    - Long-billed Ringed Plover(Charadrius placidus) (Box 14, Folder 88)
    - Caspian Plover (Charadrius asiaticus) (Box 14, Folder 89)
    - Lapwing (Vanellus vanellus) (Box 14, Folder 90)
    - Grey-headed Lapwing (Vanellus cinereus) (Box 14, Folder 91)
    - Spur-winged Plover (Hopolopterus duvaucelii) (Box 14, Folder 92)
    - Sand Plover (Charadrius peronii) (Box 14, Folder 93)
    - Oyster Catcher (Haematopus ostralegus) (Box 14, Folder 94)
    - Eastern Golden Plover (Charadrius dominicus) (Box 14, Folder 95)
    - Red-wattled Lapwing (Vanellus indicus) (Box 14, Folder 96)
  - Rostratutidae
    - Painted Snipe (Rostratula benghalensis) (Box 14, Folder 97)
  - Burhinidae
    - Stone Curlew (Burhinus magnirostris) (Box 14, Folder 98)
    - Reef Thicknee (Orthorhamphus magnirostris) (Box 14, Folder 99)
  - Laridae
    - Least Tern (Sterna albifrons) (Box 14, Folder 100)
    - Nordman Tern (Sterna hirundo) (Box 14, Folder 101)
    - Herring Gull (Larus argentatus) (Box 14, Folder 102)
    - Common Gull (Larus canus) (Box 14, Folder 103)
    - Slaty-backed Gull (Larushyperboreus) (Box 14, Folder 104)
    - Black-headed Gull (Larus ridibundus) (Box 14, Folder 105)
    - Black-tailed Gull (Larus crassirostris) (Box 14, Folder 106)
    - White-winged Black Tern (Chlidonis leucoptera) (Box 14, Folder 107)
    - Noddy Tern (Sterna pileatus) (Box 14, Folder 108)
    - Gull-billed Tern (Gelochelidon nilotica) (Box 14, Folder 109)
    - Bridled Tern (Sterna anaethetus) (Box 14, Folder 110)
    - Black-naped Tern (Sterna sumatrana) (Box 14, Folder 111)
    - Common Noddy (Anous solidus) (Box 14, Folder 112)
  - Alcidae
    - Northern Seabirds (Auks, Murres, Guillemots) (Box 15, Folder 1)